[](https://funnyjunk.com/)ZZB, LLC PRIVACY POLICY
=================================================

Who We Are and What We Do
-------------------------

ZZB, LLC is a media aggregator. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices with respect to the information we collect on behalf of our clients through our Technology, as well as the information collected on our own Web site. ZZB, LLC is committed to privacy and this Privacy Policy outlines the kinds of information we collect, how we collect information, how we use and disclose collected information, and how you can control, correct and/or update the information.

We support industry self-regulation and adhere to applicable industry guidelines. ZZB, LLC adheres to DAA principles and guidelines and is a member in good standing of industry associations that establish best practices in the area of online advertising, including the Interactive Advertising Bureau ("IAB"), the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") (including the DAA AppChoices Program for smartphones and tablets), the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (“EDAA”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (“DAAC”). ZZB, LLC adheres to the IAB Code of Conduct, the NAI Code of Conduct, the NAI Mobile Application Code and the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.

ZZB, LLC complies with the cross-industry enhanced notice standard as set forth in the Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising.

Information Collection through our Technology for Interest Based Advertising
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

### Information We Collect through our Technology

Our Technology does not collect information that can be used to directly identify an individual, such as your name, physical address, e-mail address, Social Security Number, credit card number, account numbers, passwords, personal health information or precise, real-time geographic location derived through location-based services such as GPS-enabled devices.

As part of the process of delivering ads through our Technology, we do collect information about your interaction with our Technology, your web browsing activity and your device, which in some jurisdictions may be considered personally identifiable information. This information may include information such as your device type (e.g., a computer, tablet, smartphone, gaming console or smart/connected TV), your IP address, device identifiers, non-precise location information, the date and time of your visit, browser type, web pages visited when viewing an ad, and information about your interaction with our Technology when viewing content on your device, including whether you interacted with the advertisement (viewed a video ad to completion or clicked on an ad), and what content you viewed (which advertisement we delivered to you). For example, if you visit a number of automobile-related web sites, you may be flagged as being interested in purchasing an automobile. ZZB, LLC also obtains non-PII such as behavioral, contextual and demographic information from third party providers that we can use to serve interest-based ads. ZZB, LLC may also collect Mobile Ad IDs (MAIDs) such as a Google Advertising ID (GAID) or an Apple Advertising Identifier (IDFA) as a result of running digital advertisements on behalf of our clients.

ZZB, LLC's Technology may process information to retarget an individual across multiple devices (e.g., you may receive advertisements about automobiles on your computer because based on your browsing activity on your mobile device, you have been flagged as being interested in purchasing an automobile). ZZB, LLC collects cookies and device IDs as described below, which are then fed into our proprietary cross-device algorithm, allowing ZZB, LLC to map multiple devices and cookies to one individual for the purpose of serving that user another ad on a different device. In order to provide content-relevant ads to mobile users, we may also collect carrier IDs (from US users only), information about the apps you use and the location of your device if you have elected to provide that information to the publishers with whom we have partnered.

As described in the next section, since this information is collected through cookies, we require our clients to obtain any legally required consents to allow us to place cookies on their web sites and collect information from you. Even if you consent, you can revoke your consent at any time by opting out as described below.

### How We Collect Information through our Technology

For information that we collect, directly or indirectly, we typically employ the use of "pixel tags" and/or "cookies," which are commonly used on the Internet. Pixel tags and cookies help us understand how you use a publisher's web site and the effectiveness of an ad so that we can more accurately deliver the types of ads that are relevant to your interests. Pixel tags or cookies do not in any way damage your operating system or files. You can refuse ZZB, LLC cookies, but doing so may result in the receipt of the same ads or ads that do not cater to your interests. To permanently object to the placing of ZZB, LLC cookies on your computer, you can use the opt-out process described below.

Pixel tags are small bits of code that reside on a web site and provide a method of information delivery allowing the operator of the page or a third party to collect information about the visitors to the page. Cookies are small text files that are stored on the browser of your computer that assign an anonymous identifier to your browser and provide information to the cookie sender. In addition to cookies, ZZB, LLC also uses mobile identifiers such as device IDs that are specific to an individual’s hardware, as well as statistical methods for identifying an individual across multiple devices with a high degree of accuracy.

ZZB, LLC also receives information from 3rd party data providers who collect and make available information such as behavioral, contextual, and demographic information, for our clients to use in targeting ads through our platform. For example, our clients may use health-related segments such as an inferred interest in health and wellness (e.g., personal training or gym membership). ([Click here](https://funnyjunk.com/health) for a complete list of Health-related segments provided by 3rd party data providers that may be used in ZZB, LLC's platform).

### How We Use Information Collected Through Our Technology

ZZB, LLC uses information it receives and collects through its Technology to tailor, target, and assess the effectiveness of the ads we deliver to you, and to avoid showing you the same ads repeatedly. Our analysis includes contextual and demographic elements, behaviors and viewing preferences, and we use this information to predict the characteristics and preferences of the viewers on web sites that use our Technology. We report this information to our advertiser clients in an aggregated, anonymous form to assist them in targeting their ad campaigns to a relevant Internet audience, and to our web site owner clients to gain an understanding of the general make-up of individuals who visit their site(s). Collectively, this information assists advertisers and web site owners in delivering effective ad campaigns to their audience and allows for a more relevant and meaningful ad experience for the consumer.

We may offer our clients the use of a data management platform to enable them to manage their own customer information. Each of our clients’ separate privacy policies govern the collection and use of this information. However, if you opt-out of our services by following the instructions below, you will no longer receive interest-based ads from ZZB, LLC.

Information Collection from Our Company Web Site
------------------------------------------------

We also automatically collect information via the Web site through the use of various technologies, including cookies and pixel tags. We collect IP address, browsing behavior and device IDs. We use such information collected on our Web site in pseudonymized form for internal purposes only, to administer, improve and customize the Web site and to enable us to better understand how our Web site is being used by visitors in order to enhance their overall experience.

We use cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Web site and to enable us to track and target the interests of our users to improve our online presence. Most browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can adjust the preferences in the browser of your computer or device to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or to block some or all cookies. While you may still use our Web site if you reject cookies, your ability to use some areas of our Web site may be limited. Where required by law, we collect your consent for the use of such non-essential cookies and you can always opt-out.

### Interest-Based Ads through Our Company Web Site

We, or other parties we do business with, may place or recognize unique cookies or other technologies on your browser when you visit our Web site. We, or these third parties, may use these cookies or other technologies to collect information about your use of our Web site and your other online activities over time and across different websites, and may use that information to serve interest-based advertisements to you as you browse the Internet. To learn more about such interest-based advertising, and to opt-out of such collection and use, please visit the below links of the NAI and DAA in the US:

* NAI – [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
    
* DAA – [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)
    
* DAA AppChoices – [http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices/](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices/)

To learn more about such interest-based advertising, and to opt-out of such collection and use, please visit the below links of the DAAC in Canada and the EDAA in the European Union:

* DAAC – [http://www.youradchoices.ca/choices/](http://www.youradchoices.ca/choices/)
    
* EDAA – [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

Opting Out of ZZB, LLC Technology and Reviewing Your Ad Preferences
-------------------------------------------------------------------

Your right to make informed decisions about information collection is important to ZZB, LLC. We understand that, as may be provided under applicable law, at any moment, you may exercise your right to: (1) obtain confirmation of the existence of your PII in ZZB, LLC’s database; (2) verify its content, origin and accuracy; (3) request its correction, updating, amendment, deletion or transformation into anonymous form and its blocking due to violations of the law; and (4) oppose the processing of your PII on legitimate grounds.

In the event you have provided PII to ZZB, LLC through our company Web site and wish to edit or have it removed from our database completely or to exercise your privacy rights, please contact us at [fjprivacy@gmail.com](mailto:fjprivacy@gmail.com). Please know that in order for us to respond to your request we may require that you verify your identity.

You also have the choice of opting out of receiving targeted advertising based on information collected through our Technology. Opting out will disassociate your data from ZZB, LLC’s system and will prevent you from being targeted in the future by ZZB, LLC. If you do not want to receive more relevant advertising, customized to your interests, please click here. You may also opt-out of receiving targeted advertising, by clicking on the AdChoice link within an ad served to you, or visiting the below links:

* NAI – [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
    
* DAA – [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

ZZB, LLC is an active member of the industry associations that govern the use and policies around online consumer privacy including the IAB, the DAA in the US (including the DAA AppChoices Program for smartphones and tablets), the DAAC ([www.youradchoices.ca](http://www.youradchoices.ca/)), the EDAA ([www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)) and the NAI ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)). ZZB, LLC complies with the IAB Code of Conduct, the NAI Code of Conduct and the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. We believe that these codes and principles help protect and ensure individual consumer privacy. ZZB, LLC also uses a DAA-Approved platform to comply with the ‘Enhanced Notice' standard as dictated by the cross-industry Self-Regulation Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. As part of this service, advertisements served by ZZB, LLC's platform or other parties we do business with, are sometimes delivered with icons that serve as a signal to consumers that behavioral information has been used. Through the icon, consumers can learn how their information is being used and by what companies, and access tools to control the collection and use of their information.

When you opt-out of receiving interest-based ads from ZZB, LLC, we will place a cookie in your web browser that identifies you as opted-out. Our Technology will recognize your opt-out cookie and will preclude advertisers using ZZB, LLC Technology from displaying interest-based ads to you. However, the choice to opt-out is unique to the browser in which you set it and you may need to repeat your opt-out election if you use a different computer or change browsers. Also, the opt-out cookie cannot be set if your browser is configured to block third-party cookies. Opting out via this method does not prevent the use of cookies or similar means that are necessary for the operation of the Web site or other legitimate purposes unrelated to serving interest-based ads. Information may still be collected about your web browsing activities for these other purposes. While you will not receive ads based on your interests derived from your online behavior, you will still see advertising, including contextual ads that are based on the content of the web page that you visit.

Information Sharing and Disclosures
-----------------------------------

Except for information collected through the Technology and provided to our clients, affiliates, partners, and service providers to operate or enhance our services for the purposes described above, or as required by law, ZZB, LLC does not rent, sell or share the information collected through the Technology with third parties.

In providing its Technology services, ZZB, LLC works with a variety of third-party vendors and partners. These include advertisers, publishers, data providers, content providers, and other service providers. ZZB, LLC may share non-PII with them, including statistical, demographic, contextual, behavioral and predictive information, about our users and their use of the Technology, to the extent necessary for ZZB, LLC to provide the Technology services. We may also enhance the non-PII collected via our Technology with non-PII collected from trusted business partners. ZZB, LLCu endeavors to keep such information in an anonymous non-PII format, which cannot be used to contact or identify any person individually.

ZZB, LLC may share information about individuals as it deems reasonably necessary in order to comply with applicable law, to exercise and protect the legal rights of ZZB, LLC or its personnel and representatives, and to investigate, prevent or respond to suspected illicit activities, including fraud and threats of harm to individuals.

If ZZB, LLC sells all or part of its business, or if any of its departments or technology is acquired or merged with another company, we may transfer information about you, including PII submitted by you on our Web site, to the successor company as part of that transaction. To the extent consent is required under applicable law for such a data transfer, we will obtain your consent.

Cross-border Data Transfers
---------------------------

Our Technology and Web site is operated in accordance with the laws of the United States. Given that we are an international business, our use of your information necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. If you are located in Mexico, the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect may be transferred to and processed in the United States and other applicable territories in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as or equivalent to those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

Security
--------

ZZB, LLC has established appropriate technical and organizational safeguards consistent with industry standards and applicable law to help prevent unauthorized access, loss, disclosure, modification or destruction of the information we collect. While we are committed to ensuring the security of such information, you should be aware that no data protection measures can provide 100% guarantee of security. Consequently, we -- like everyone else -- cannot warrant or guarantee the complete security of the information in our possession.

Information Retention
---------------------

ZZB, LLC sets cookies to expire after ninety days and the expiration date refreshes every time you encounter our server through our Technology. After ninety days we remove cookie information from information collected through our Technology and retain web log data, aggregations and reports for as long as necessary for the purposes for which such information is collected as described in this Privacy Policy and to comply with applicable legal requirements. ZZB, LLC removes mobile device ID information from information collected through our Technology every five years and retains web log data, aggregations and reports for as long as necessary for the purposes for which such information is collected as described in this Privacy Policy and to comply with applicable legal requirements.

Third Party Advertisers and Links
---------------------------------

ZZB, LLC's Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by third-party advertisers, web site owners, data providers, or other parties that we may do business with, or other parties linked to our company Web site or otherwise accessible via our Technology. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through ZZB, LLC Technology and by this Web site. The information collected or received by any third-party or provider is subject to that company's own privacy policy.

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by ZZB, LLC. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties or the privacy policies governing their web sites.

California Do Not Track
-----------------------

When you turn on Do Not Track (DNT) in your browser, ZZB, LLC responds by not collecting your information, either directly or through third parties, for the purpose of serving interest-based ads based on your browsing history.

Children's Privacy
------------------

We do not knowingly collect PII from, and do not create user segments targeted for children under 13 years of age. If you believe your child or someone else has provided ZZB, LLC with PII about your child and you would like to have the information removed, please contact us and we will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from our records.

How to Contact Us
-----------------

If you have any questions or concerns about ZZB, LLC's Privacy Policy, you may contact us at this email address: [fjprivacy@gmail.com](mailto:fjprivacy@gmail.com), or you can send correspondence to the following address:

ZZB, LLC  
335 Hudson, 11th Floor, #232  
New York, New York 10014

Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information
---------------------------------------------------------

ZZB, LLC may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and you will be informed of such changes through a notice posted on our Web site. Your continued use of the Web site after we make changes to this Privacy Policy is deemed acknowledgement of those changes, so please review this Privacy Policy periodically. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of our Technology as well as for special feature and services not described in this Privacy Policy that may be introduced in the future.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 05/21/2018.
